{
	"cards": [
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-vocabulary-card-1",
			"front": "Fixed-wing and rotary-wing (known as helicopters) aircraft that have been modified for medical care; used to evacuate and transport patients with life-threatening injuries to treatment facilities.",
			"back": "air ambulances"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-vocabulary-card-2",
			"front": "A specialized vehicle for treating and transporting sick and injured patients.",
			"back": "ambulance"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-vocabulary-card-3",
			"front": "Areas of the road that are blocked from your view by your vehicle or mirrors.",
			"back": "blind spots"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-vocabulary-card-4",
			"front": "The process of removing dirt, dust, blood, or other visible contaminants from a surface.",
			"back": "cleaning"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-vocabulary-card-5",
			"front": "A device that provides a firm surface under the patientâ€™s torso.",
			"back": "CPR board"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-vocabulary-card-6",
			"front": "A safe distance between your vehicle and any vehicles around you.",
			"back": "cushion of safety"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-vocabulary-card-7",
			"front": "To remove or neutralize radiation, chemical, or other hazardous material from clothing, equipment, vehicles, and personnel.",
			"back": "decontaminate"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-vocabulary-card-8",
			"front": "The killing of pathogenic agents by direct application of chemicals.",
			"back": "disinfection"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-vocabulary-card-9",
			"front": "Specialized vehicles used to transport EMS equipment and personnel to the scenes of medical emergencies.",
			"back": "first-responder vehicles"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-vocabulary-card-10",
			"front": "The killing of pathogenic agents by using potent means of disinfection.",
			"back": "high-level disinfection"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-vocabulary-card-11",
			"front": "Occurs when the tires of a vehicle are lifted off the road surface as a result of water piling up underneath them, making the vehicle feel as though it is floating.",
			"back": "hydroplaning"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-vocabulary-card-12",
			"front": "A portable kit containing items that are used in the initial care of the patient.",
			"back": "jump kit"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-vocabulary-card-13",
			"front": "Medical evacuation of a patient by helicopter.",
			"back": "medevac"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-vocabulary-card-14",
			"front": "A person who assists a driver in backing up an ambulance to help adjust for blind spots at the back of the vehicle.",
			"back": "spotter"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-vocabulary-card-15",
			"front": "The six-pointed star emblem that identifies vehicles that meet federal specifications as licensed or certified ambulances.",
			"back": "Star of Life"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-38-tag-vocabulary-card-16",
			"front": "A process, such as heating, that removes microbial contamination.",
			"back": "sterilization"
		}
	],
	"category": {
		"value": "chapter-38",
		"label": "Chapter 38"
	},
	"tags": [
		{
			"value": "vocabulary",
			"label": "Vocabulary"
		}
	]
}